Massachusetts Campus Compact Records MS128
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Massachusetts Campus Compact Grants: IN and After School Grant Program, SEAMS, 1995 -- 2002; MS128.002; 8.4 Linear Feet
  - After School Grant Program - Merrimack College, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - After School Grant Program - Northern Essex Community College NOT AWARDED, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - After School Grant Program - Quinsigamond Community College, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - After School Grant Program - Regis College, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - After School Grant Program - Smith College, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - After School Grant Program - Stonehill College, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - After School Grant Program - Suffolk University, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - After School Grant Program - Tufts Medical School NOT AWARDED, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - After School Grant Program - Tufts School of Veterinary Medicine, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - After School Grant Program - Tufts University: Engineering, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - After School Grant Program - Tufts University: TLC, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - After School Grant Program - UMASS Medical School NOT AWARDED, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Berkshire Community College In and AS Grant Application, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Boston College In and AS Grant Application, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Bridgewater State College In and AS Grant Application, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Bristol Community College (semester) In and AS Grant Application, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Cape Cod Community College In and AS Grant Application, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Elms College In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Fitchburg State College (new) In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Fitchburg State College (renewal) In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Gordon College In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Hampshire College In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Harvard University In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Holyoke Community College In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Lesley University In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Massachusetts College of Art In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Mass College of Liberal Arts In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Massasoit Community College In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Merrimack College In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Mt. Ida College In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Mt. Wachusett Community College In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - MIT In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Newbury College In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Northern Essex Community College In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Regis College In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - School of the MFA, Boston In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Smith College In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Springfield College In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Stonehill College In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Tufts University In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - UMASS Amherst In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - UMASS Amherst (semester) In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - UMASS Lowell In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - Western New England College In and AS Grant Application, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.002.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - After School Grant Program Application: Amherst College-Not Accepted, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - After School Grant Program Application: Boston University/Hillel-Not Accepted, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - After School Grant Program Application: Hampshire College-Not Accepted, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - After School Grant Program Application: Regis College-Not Accepted, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - After School Grant Program Application: Wheelock College-Not Accepted, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Bentley College, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Boston University: HIV/AIDS, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - College of Our Lady of the Elms, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Colleges of Worcester Consortium, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Hampshire College: the Media Literacy Project, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Harvard Outward Bound Project, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Mount Wachusett Community College, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Northeastern University, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Northern Essex Community College, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Simmons College, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Stonehill College, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Tufts Veterinary School, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Wellesley College, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - UMASS Amherst, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - MACC After School: Proposals--Not Accepted, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Amherst College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Amherst College Year-End Report, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Bentley College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Bentley College Year-End Report, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Berkshire Community College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Berkshire Community College Year-End Report, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Boston College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Boston College Year-End Report, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Bridgewater State College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Bridgewater State College Year-End Report, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.006.00030 (Box 6)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Colleges of Worcester Consortium, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.006.00031 (Box 6)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Dean College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.006.00032 (Box 6)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Dean College Year-End Report, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.006.00033 (Box 6)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Fitchburg State College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.006.00034 (Box 6)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Fitchburg State College Year-End Report, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.006.00035 (Box 6)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Hampshire College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Harvard University, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Harvard University Year-End Report, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Middlesex Community College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Middlesex Community College Year-End Report, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Mount Ida College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Mount Wachusett Community College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Northeastern University, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Northeastern University Year-End Report, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Northern Essex Community College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Quinsigamond Community College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Salem State College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Salem State College Year-End Report, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Simmons College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Stonehill College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Stonehill College Year-End Report, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: UMASS Boston, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: UMASS Boston Year-End Report, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - MACC After School Grant Program: Worcester State College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00019 (Box 7)
  - SEAMS: Berkshire Community College, 1995 -- 1996; MS128.002.007.00020 (Box 7)
  - SEAMS: Correspondence with Berkshire Community College, 1995 -- 1996; MS128.002.007.00021 (Box 7)
  - SEAMS: Correspondence with UMASS/Lowell, 1995 -- 1996; MS128.002.007.00022 (Box 7)
  - SEAMS: Proposals, 1995 -- 1996; MS128.002.007.00023 (Box 7)
  - SEAMS: Grantee--Lasell College, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.007.00024 (Box 7)
  - SEAMS: Grantee--Middlesex Community College, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.007.00025 (Box 7)
  - SEAMS: Grantee--Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.007.00026 (Box 7)
  - SEAMS: Proposal Applicants, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.002.007.00027 (Box 7)
  - SEAMS: Middlesex Community College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00028 (Box 7)
  - SEAMS: Wheaton College, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.002.007.00029 (Box 7)
- Higher Education Consortium Grant Programs, 1992 -- 1997; MS128.003; 4.8 Linear Feet
  This series contains early grant programs through the Higher Education Consortium. These grant programs are also sponsored under the titles/agency of Massachusetts Community Service Commission (MCSC) and the Campus Consortia for Community Service. Grant programs include Higher Education Innovative Projects for Community Service, Learn and Serve Consortium, and direct grant applications to the Corporation for National Service.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by grant, then chronologically within the grant, then alphabetically within years.
  - CNS: Direct Applications to the Corporation for National Service, Folder 1, 1994; MS128.003.001.00008 (Box MS128 Shared 1)
  - CNS: Direct Applications to the Corporation for National Service, Folder 2, 1994; MS128.003.001.00009 (Box MS128 Shared 1)
  - CNS: Direct Applications to the Corporation for National Service, Folder 3, 1994; MS128.003.001.00010 (Box MS128 Shared 1)
  - CNS: Direct Applications to the Corporation for National Service, 1995; MS128.003.001.00011 (Box MS128 Shared 1)
  - CNS: Funded Direct Applications to the Corporation for National Service, Folder 1, 1994 -- 1996; MS128.003.001.00012 (Box MS128 Shared 1)
  - CNS: Funded Direct Applications to the Corporation for National Service, Folder 2, 1994 -- 1996; MS128.003.001.00013 (Box MS128 Shared 1)
  - CNS: Boston University, 1995; MS128.003.001.00014 (Box MS128 Shared 1)
  - CNS: Northern Essex Community College, Folder 1, 1994 -- 1995; MS128.003.001.00015 (Box MS128 Shared 1)
  - CNS: Northern Essex Community College, Folder 2, 1994 -- 1995; MS128.003.001.00016 (Box MS128 Shared 1)
  - Educational Development Center, 1995; MS128.003.001.00017 (Box MS128 Shared 1)
  - Higher Education Consortium Applications, Folder 1, 1994; MS128.003.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Higher Education Consortium Applications, Folder 2, 1994; MS128.003.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: Bentley College Service Learning, Folder 1, 1995; MS128.003.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: Bentley College Service Learning, Folder 2, 1995; MS128.003.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: Bentley College Kids and Elders, 1994 -- 1995; MS128.003.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: Bentley College Info Packets, 1995 -- 1996; MS128.003.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: Bradford College, Folder 1, 1994 -- 1995; MS128.003.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: Bradford College, Folder 2, 1995 -- 1996; MS128.003.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: Harvard/Outward Bound, Folder 1, 1995 -- 1997; MS128.003.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: Harvard/Outward Bound, Folder 2, 1995; MS128.003.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: Lasell College, 1994 -- 1997; MS128.003.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: Lesley College, Folder 1, 1994 -- 1996; MS128.003.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: Lesley College, Folder 2, 1995 -- 1997; MS128.003.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: Lesley College, Folder 3, 1995; MS128.003.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: Middlesex Community College, Folder 1, 1994 -- 1995; MS128.003.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: Middlesex Community College, Folder 2, 1994 -- 1995; MS128.003.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: Middlesex Community College, Folder 3, 1995 -- 1997; MS128.003.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: Middlesex Community College, Folder 4, 1994 -- 1995; MS128.003.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: UMASS/Gerontology Institute, Folder 1, 1994 -- 1996; MS128.003.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: UMASS/Gerontology Institute, Folder 2, 1995 -- 1996; MS128.003.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Consortium Grantees: UMASS/Gerontology Institute, Folder 3, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.003.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Innovation Project, 1992; MS128.003.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Innovation Project, Folder 1, 1993; MS128.003.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Innovation Project, Folder 2, 1993; MS128.003.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Learn and Serve Consortium Grant Information, Year I, Folder 1, 1994 -- 1995; MS128.003.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Learn and Serve Consortium Grant Information, Year I, Folder 2, 1994 -- 1995; MS128.003.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Learn and Serve Consortium Grant Information, Year II, Folder 1, 1995 -- 1996; MS128.003.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Learn and Serve Consortium Grant Information, Year II, Folder 2, 1995 -- 1996; MS128.003.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Learn and Serve Consortium Grant Information, Year III, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.003.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Requests for Proposals, 1992 -- 1994; MS128.003.004.00005 (Box 4)